Code	NACE_R2
A01	Crop and animal production, hunting and related service activities
A02	Forestry and logging
A03	Fishing and aquaculture
B	Mining and quarrying
C10-C12	"Manufacture of food products; beverages and tobacco products"
C13-C15	Manufacture of textiles, wearing apparel, leather and related products
C16	"Manufacture of wood and of products of wood and cork, except furniture; manufacture of articles of straw and plaiting materials"
C17	Manufacture of paper and paper products
C18	Printing and reproduction of recorded media
C19	Manufacture of coke and refined petroleum products
C20	Manufacture of chemicals and chemical products
C21	Manufacture of basic pharmaceutical products and pharmaceutical preparations
C22	Manufacture of rubber and plastic products
C23	Manufacture of other non-metallic mineral products
C24	Manufacture of basic metals
C25	Manufacture of fabricated metal products, except machinery and equipment
C26	Manufacture of computer, electronic and optical products
C27	Manufacture of electrical equipment
C28	Manufacture of machinery and equipment n.e.c.
C29	Manufacture of motor vehicles, trailers and semi-trailers
C30	Manufacture of other transport equipment
C31_C32	"Manufacture of furniture; other manufacturing"
C33	Repair and installation of machinery and equipment
D35	Electricity, gas, steam and air conditioning supply
E36	Water collection, treatment and supply
E37-E39	Sewerage, waste management, remediation activities
F	Construction
G45	Wholesale and retail trade and repair of motor vehicles and motorcycles
G46	Wholesale trade, except of motor vehicles and motorcycles
G47	Retail trade, except of motor vehicles and motorcycles
H49	Land transport and transport via pipelines
H50	Water transport
H51	Air transport
H52	Warehousing and support activities for transportation
H53	Postal and courier activities
I	Accommodation and food service activities
J58	Publishing activities
J59_J60	"Motion picture, video, television programme production; programming and broadcasting activities"
J61	Telecommunications
J62_J63	Computer programming, consultancy, and information service activities
K64	Financial service activities, except insurance and pension funding
K65	Insurance, reinsurance and pension funding, except compulsory social security
K66	Activities auxiliary to financial services and insurance activities
L68B	Real estate activities
L68A	Imputed rents of owner-occupied dwellings
M69_M70	"Legal and accounting activities; activities of head offices; management consultancy activities"
M71	"Architectural and engineering activities; technical testing and analysis"
M72	Scientific research and development
M73	Advertising and market research
M74_M75	"Other professional, scientific and technical activities; veterinary activities"
N77	Rental and leasing activities
N78	Employment activities
N79	Travel agency, tour operator reservation service and related activities
N80-N82	Security and investigation, service and landscape, office administrative and support activities
O84	"Public administration and defence; compulsory social security"
P85	Education
Q86	Human health activities
Q87_Q88	Residential care activities and social work activities without accommodation
R90-R92	"Creative, arts and entertainment activities; libraries, archives, museums and other cultural activities; gambling and betting activities"
R93	Sports activities and amusement and recreation activities
S94	Activities of membership organisations
S95	Repair of computers and personal and household goods
S96	Other personal service activities
T	"Activities of households as employers; undifferentiated goods- and services-producing activities of households for own use"
U	Activities of extraterritorial organisations and bodies